Here I have another style of a criss cross strap, in a back view.
What I have done here, is show that the garment that it's criss crossing and attached to.
is going straight across the back.
There is your seam lines.
But the criss cross factor and remember this is a back view.
Because, I cut off her head.
When you see that, that means it's on the back.
I also have indicated back view, if you can't read it.
But the criss cross means that over, under, over, under.
Like they're braided.
Only they're not braided.
But they criss cross each other.
They don't just cross.
They criss cross.
So there's cross and there's criss cross.
And then, it doesn't have to have, necessarily this many straps.
It could have more straps than this.
What it's showing is that somehow probably, they are going to be sewn in, to the back of it.
And maybe they attach in the front.
Or maybe they're stretchy.
And it just gets, put over the head.
But this is just another version of a criss cross strap for neck.